Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part Two
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Autograph Items by Category, 1666-1961; Series I; 12.1; (32 boxes)
  - POLITICAL FIGURES
    - Eden, Anthony, Earl of Avon, b. 1897, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 973)
    - Eglington, Archibald William Montgomerie, Earl of, 1812-1861, 1846 (Box 20, Folder 974)
    - Eldon, John Scott, Earl of, 1751-1838, 1803-28, undated (Box 20, Folder 975)
    - Ellenborough, Edward Law, Earl of, 1790-1871, 1830-66, undated (Box 20, Folder 976)
    - Ellesmere, Francis Egerton, Earl, 1800-1857, 1842 (Box 20, Folder 977)
    - Ellis, Wellbore, 1713-1802, 1782 (Box 20, Folder 978)
    - Erskine, Thomas Erskine, baron, 1750- 1823, 1783 (Box 20, Folder 979)
    - Everett, Alexander Hill, 1790-1847, undated (Box 20, Folder 980)
    - Everett, Edward, 1794-1865, 1861 (Box 20, Folder 981)
    - Exeter, William Alleyne Cecil, Marquess of, 1825-1895, 1864-74, undated (Box 20, Folder 982)
    - Fawcett, Henry, 1833-1884, 1883 (Box 20, Folder 983)
    - Fitzgerald, William Robert Seymour, Sir (Box 20, Folder 984)
    - Fitzherbert, William, 1712-1772, 1759 (Box 20, Folder 985)
    - Forster, W.E. (William Edward), 1818- 1886, 1874 (Box 20, Folder 986)
    - Fox, Charles James, 1749-1806, 1795 (Box 20, Folder 987)
    - Fox, Georgiana L., undated (Box 20, Folder 988)
    - Frere, Bartle, Sir, 1815-1884, 1872-84, undated (Box 20, Folder 989)
    - Gardner, James Tynte Agg-, Sir, 1846- 1928, undated (Box 20, Folder 990)
    - Garnett, William, 1793-1873, 1837 (Box 20, Folder 991)
    - Gladstone, Catherine, Mrs., d. 1901, 1875, undated (Box 20, Folder 992)
    - Gladstone, Herbert John Gladstone, Viscount, 1854-1930, 1889 (Box 20, Folder 993)
    - Gladstone, W.E. (William Ewart), 1809- 1898, 1854-88, undated (Box 20, Folder 994)
    - Glenelg, Charles Grant, Baron, 1778- 1866, 1838-56, undated (Box 20, Folder 995)
    - Goldsmid, Julian, Sir, 1838-1896, 1865, undated (Box 20, Folder 996)
    - Gooch, Edward Sherlock, Sir, d. 1856, undated (Box 20, Folder 997)
    - Gower, Ronald Sutherland, Lord, 1845- 1916, 1887-1915, undated (Box 20, Folder 998)
    - Graham, James, Sir, 1792-1861, 1815 (Box 20, Folder 999)
    - Grant Duff, Arthur Cunningham, 1861- 1948, 1915 (Box 20, Folder 1000)
    - Grant Duff, Mountstuart E. (Mountstuart Elphinstone), Sir, 1829- 1906, 1871-92 (Box 20, Folder 1001)
    - Grantley, Fletcher Norton, Baron, 1798-1875, 1857 (Box 20, Folder 1002)
    - Grenville, William Wyndham Grenville, Baron, 1759-1834, 1827 (Box 20, Folder 1003)
    - Greville, Charles, 1794-1865, 1853 (Box 20, Folder 1004)
    - Grey, Charles, 1804-1870, 1851-55 (Box 20, Folder 1005)
    - Grey, Charles Grey, Earl, 1764-1845, 1812-35 (Box 20, Folder 1006)
    - Grey, George, Sir, 1799-1882, 1840-60, undated (Box 20, Folder 1007)
    - Grey, Henry George Grey, Earl, 1802- 1894, 1843-67, undated (Box 20, Folder 1008)
    - Grosvenor, R. (Robert), Lord, 1801- 1893, undated (Box 20, Folder 1009)
    - Gurdon, William Brampton, Sir, 1840- 1901 (Box 20, Folder 1010)
    - Halifax, Charles Wood, Viscount, 1800- 1885, 1856 (Box 20, Folder 1011)
    - Halsbury, Hardinge Stanley Giffard, Earl of, 1823-1921, undated (Box 20, Folder 1012)
    - Hamilton, William Alexander Baillie, 1844-1920, 1890 (Box 20, Folder 1013)
    - Harcourt, Lady E.C. Vernon, 1911, undated (Box 20, Folder 1014)
    - Harcourt, William Vernon, Sir, 1827- 1904, 1867 (Box 20, Folder 1015)
    - Hatherley, William Page Wood, Baron, 1801-1881, 1859-65 (Box 20, Folder 1016)
    - Hewart, Gordon Hewart, Baron, 1870- 1943, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 1017)
    - Holdernesse, Robert Darcy, Earl of, 1718-1778, 1756 (Box 20, Folder 1018)
    - Holland, Henry Richard Vassall, Baron, 1773-1840, 1833 (Box 20, Folder 1019)
    - Japan, Minister to Great Britain, 1877 (Box 21, Folder 1020)
    - Kenealy, Edward Vaughan, 1819-1880, 1873, undated (Box 21, Folder 1021)
    - Knatchbull, Edward, Sir, 1781-1849, 1842-56 (Box 21, Folder 1022)
    - Lang, Robert, 1681 (Box 21, Folder 1023)
    - Loreburn, Robert T. Reid (Robert Threshie Reid), Earl, 1846-1923, 1882 (Box 21, Folder 1024)
    - Lygon, Frederick, Earl Beauchamp, 1830-1891, 1887 (Box 21, Folder 1025)
    - Lytton, Edward, Bulwer Lytton, Baron, 1803-1873, 1839-63, undated (Box 21, Folder 1026)
    - Maloney, Cornelius, Alfred, Sir, 1849- 1913, 1886-91, undated (Box 21, Folder 1027)
    - Martin, Samuel, Sir, 1801-1883, 1881 (Box 21, Folder 1028)
    - Mazzini, Giuseppe, 1805-1872, undated (Box 21, Folder 1029)
    - Meaghner, Thomas Francis, 1823-1867, 1849 (Box 21, Folder 1030)
    - Melchett, Alfred Moritz Mond, Baron, 1868-1930, undated (Box 21, Folder 1031)
    - Monk, Charles James, 1824-1900, 1879 (Box 21, Folder 1032)
    - Monroe, James, 1758-1831, undated (Box 21, Folder 1033)
    - Mulcahy, Richard James, 1886-1971, undated (Box 21, Folder 1034)
    - North, Frederick, Lord, 1732-1792, 1759 (Box 21, Folder 1035)
    - Northbrook, Thomas George Baring, Earl of, 1826-1904, 1876-92 (Box 21, Folder 1036)
    - Norton, C.B. Adderley (Charles Bowyer Adderley), Baron, 1814-1905, 1852 (Box 21, Folder 1037)
    - Ossington, John Evelyn Denison, Viscount, 1800-1873, 1860-68, undated (Box 21, Folder 1038)
    - Peel, Arthur Wellesley, Sir, 1829-1912, undated (Box 21, Folder 1039)
    - Peel, Robert, Sir, 1788-1850, 1829-41 (Box 21, Folder 1040)
    - Perceval, John, Earl, 1683-1748, 1731 (Box 21, Folder 1041)
    - Pirbright, Henry de Worms, Baron, 1840-1903, 1890 (Box 21, Folder 1042)
    - Pitt, William, Earl of Chatham, 1708- 1778, 1774 (Box 21, Folder 1043)
    - Pleydell-Bouverie, Edward, 1881-1889, 1875 (Box 21, Folder 1044)
    - Portland, William Henry Cavendish- Bentinck, Duke of, 1738-1809, 1788 (Box 21, Folder 1045)
    - Primrose, H.W., b. 1846, 1886 (Box 21, Folder 1046)
    - Rendlesham, Frederick William Brook, Baron, 1840-1911, 1906 (Box 21, Folder 1047)
    - Rhett, Sarah, d. 1808, 1787 (Box 21, Folder 1048)
    - Ripon, Frederick John Robinson, Earl of, 1782-1859, 1824-34 (Box 21, Folder 1049)
    - Ritz, John, 1863 (Box 21, Folder 1050)
    - Rolle of Stevenstone, John Rolle, Baron, 1750-1842, 1780 (Box 21, Folder 1051)
    - Rowton, Montagu William Lowry-Corry, Baron, 1838-1903, undated (Box 21, Folder 1052)
    - Russell, John Russell, Earl, 1792-1878, 1825-78, undated (Box 21, Folder 1053)
    - Sackville, George Germain, Viscount, 1716-1785, 1756 (Box 21, Folder 1054)
    - Salkeld, George, for the State of Louisiana, 1831 (Box 21, Folder 1055)
    - Schomburgk, Robert H. (Robert Hermann), Sir, 1804-1865, 1848 (Box 21, Folder 1056)
    - Selborne, Roundell Palmer, Earl of, 1812-1895, 1853-95, undated (Box 21, Folder 1057)
    - Shaftesbury, Anthony Ashley Cooper, Earl of, 1801-1885, 1848-72 (Box 21, Folder 1058)
    - Sidmouth, Henry Addington, Viscount, 1757-1844, 1813-43 (Box 21, Folder 1059)
    - Storks, Henry, Sir, 1811-1874, 1864 (Box 21, Folder 1060)
    - Sugden, Edward Burtenshaw, 1781-1875, 1849 (Box 21, Folder 1061)
    - Sydney, Thomas Townshend, Viscount, 1733-1800, 1791 (Box 21, Folder 1062)
    - Temple, Richard, Sir, 1826-1902, 1881 (Box 21, Folder 1063)
    - Thornton, Edward, Sir, 1817-1906, 1881 (Box 21, Folder 1064)
    - Truman, Benjamin Cummings, 1835-1916, 1910 (Box 21, Folder 1065)
    - Wemyss, Francis Wemyss Charteris Douglas, Earl of, 1818-1914, undated (Box 21, Folder 1066)
    - Westminster, Richard Grosvenor, Marquis of, 1795-1869, 1809-61, undated (Box 21, Folder 1067)
    - Winchilsea, George William Finch- Hatton, Earl of, 1791-1858, 1834-45 (Box 21, Folder 1068)
  - POSTAL HISTORY
    - Bagot, Lewis, 1741-1802, 1792 (Box 22, Folder 1069)
    - Beaufort, Henry Charles Somerset, Duke of, 1766-1835, 1817 (Box 22, Folder 1070)
    - Berwick, William Noel-Hill, 1802-1882, 1867 (Box 22, Folder 1071)
    - Boston, William Irby, Baron, 1707-1775, 1766 (Box 22, Folder 1072)
    - Browne, F. Napier, 1875 (Box 22, Folder 1073)
    - Callaghan, W., 1838 (Box 22, Folder 1074)
    - Chassereau, Francis, 1828 (Box 22, Folder 1075)
    - Donegal, Marquis, 1769-1844, 1829 (Box 22, Folder 1076)
    - Erroll, William Hay, Earl of, 1772- 1819, 1806 (Box 22, Folder 1077)
    - Falkland, Lucius Bentinck Cary, Viscount, 1803-1884, 1845 (Box 22, Folder 1078)
    - Forbes, Baron, 1765-1843, 1832 (Box 22, Folder 1079)
    - Houghton, Richard Monckton Milnes, Baron, 1809-1885, 1839 (Box 22, Folder 1080)
    - Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806- 1863, 1855 (Box 22, Folder 1081)
    - Long, R., 1816 (Box 22, Folder 1082)
    - Marsh, J.W.D., 1819 (Box 22, Folder 1083)
    - Minto, Gilbert Elliot, Earl of, 1751- 1814, 1786 (Box 22, Folder 1084)
    - Newcastle, Henry Pelham Fiennes Pelham Clinton, Duke of, 1785-1851, 1828 (Box 22, Folder 1085)
    - Perceval, Alexander, 1787-1858, 1838 (Box 22, Folder 1086)
    - Pirbright, Henry de Worms, Baron, 1840-1903, 1888 (Box 22, Folder 1087)
    - Pomfret, Thomas William Fermor, Earl of, 1770-1833, 1807 (Box 22, Folder 1088)
    - Powis, Edward Herbert, Earl of, 1785- 1848, 1825 (Box 22, Folder 1089)
    - Ribblesdale, Thomas Lister, Baron, 1752-1826, 1804 (Box 22, Folder 1090)
    - Rochford, William Nassau de Zuylestein, Earl of, 1754-1830, 1806 (Box 22, Folder 1091)
    - Stradbroke, John Rous, Earl, 1750-1827, 1813 (Box 22, Folder 1092)
    - Unidentified, 1855 (Box 22, Folder 1093)
    - Unidentified, 1825 (Box 22, Folder 1094)
  - ROYAL FAMILY
    - Albany, Helena, Duchess of, 1861-1922, 1884-86, undated (Box 23, Folder 1095)
    - Albert Victor, Prince, Duke of Clarence and Avondale, 1864-1892, 1875, undated (Box 23, Folder 1096)
    - Alice, Grand Duchess, consort of Ludwig IV, Grand Duke of Hesse- Darmstadt, 1843-1878, undated (Box 23, Folder 1097)
    - Arthur, Duke of Connaught, 1850-1942, undated (Box 23, Folder 1098)
    - Augusta Sophia, Princess of Great Britain, 1768-1840, 1827 (Box 23, Folder 1099)
    - Augustus Frederick, Duke of Sussex, 1773-1843, 1830-38 (Box 23, Folder 1100)
    - Beatrice, Princess, consort of Henry, Prince of Battenberg, 1857-1944, undated (Box 23, Folder 1101)
    - Cambridge, George William Frederick Charles, Duke of, 1819-1904, 1839-96, undated (Box 23, Folder 1102)
    - Edward VII, King of Great Britain, 1841-1910, undated (Box 23, Folder 1103)
    - Ernest Augustus, King of Hanover, 1771-1851, 1821 (Box 23, Folder 1104)
    - Frederick Augustus, Duke of York and Albany, 1763-1827, 1818 (Box 23, Folder 1105)
    - Helena Augusta Victoria, Princess Christian of Schleswig-Holstein, 1846- 1923, undated (Box 23, Folder 1106)
    - Leopold, Duke of Albany, 1853-1884, 1877, undated (Box 23, Folder 1107)
    - Louise, Princess, Duchess of Argyll, 1848-1939, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 1108)
    - Marie Louise, Princess, 1872-1956, 1910 (Box 23, Folder 1109)
    - Mary, Princess, Duchess of Teck, 1833- 1897, undated (Box 23, Folder 1110)
    - Saxe-Coburg and Gotha, Alfred, Duke of, 1844-1900, 1864, undated (Box 23, Folder 1111)
    - Victoria, Queen of Great Britain, 1819-1901, 1857-76, undated (Box 23, Folder 1112)
    - William IV, King of Great Britain, 1765-1837, 1821 (Box 23, Folder 1113)
    - William Frederick, Duke of Gloucester, 1776-1834, 1815 (Box 23, Folder 1114)
  - SCIENTISTS
    - Abney, William de Wiveleslie, Sir, 1843-1920, undated (Box 24, Folder 1115)
    - Airy, George Biddell, Sir, 1801-1892, 1866 (Box 24, Folder 1116)
    - Allman, George James, 1812-1898, undated (Box 24, Folder 1117)
    - Andrews, Charles William, 1866-1924, 1906, undated (Box 24, Folder 1118)
    - Ansted, D.T. (David Thomas), 1814-1880, undated (Box 24, Folder 1119)
    - Anthropological Society of London, 1865 (Box 24, Folder 1120)
    - Argyll, George Douglas Campbell, Duke of, 1823-1900, 1893-95, undated (Box 24, Folder 1121)
    - Armstrong, W.G. (William George), Baron, 1810-1900, 1874-77, undated (Box 24, Folder 1122)
    - Arnott, George Arnold Walker, 1799- 1868, undated (Box 24, Folder 1123)
    - Arnott, Neil, 1788-1874, 1845 (Box 24, Folder 1124)
    - Ashburton, William Bingham Baring, Baron, 1799-1864, 1861 (Box 24, Folder 1125)
    - Aylesford, Lady, d. 1832, 1814 (Box 24, Folder 1126)
    - Babbage, Charles, 1791-1871, 1858 (Box 24, Folder 1127)
    - Bacon, John Mackenzie, 1846-1904, 1901 (Box 24, Folder 1128)
    - Badham, David, 1806-1857, undated (Box 24, Folder 1129)
    - Bagot, William Bagot, Baron, 1773-1856, undated (Box 24, Folder 1130)
    - Baillie, Edmund J., 1893 (Box 24, Folder 1131)
    - Balfour, John Hutton, 1808-1884, 1875, undated (Box 24, Folder 1132)
    - Ball, Robert S. (Robert Stawell), Sir, 1840-1913, 1892, undated (Box 24, Folder 1133)
    - Ball, W.W. Rose (Walter William Rose), 1850-1925, 1908 (Box 24, Folder 1134)
    - Barlow, Peter, 1776-1862, undated (Box 24, Folder 1135)
    - Barrett, William, Sir, 1844-1925, undated (Box 24, Folder 1136)
    - Barroit, Charles, 1897 (Box 24, Folder 1137)
    - Bayly, William, 1737-1810, undated (Box 24, Folder 1138)
    - Beadon, Frederick, 1777-1879, 1878 (Box 24, Folder 1139)
    - Beddard, Frank E. (Frank Evers), 1858- 1925, 1890 (Box 24, Folder 1140)
    - Bell, Ernest Albert, 1851-1933, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 1141)
    - Bennett, Alfred W. (Alfred William), 1833-1902, undated (Box 24, Folder 1142)
    - Blumenbach, Johann Friedrich, 1752- 1840, undated (Box 24, Folder 1143)
    - Boulenger, George Albert, 1858-1957, 1894 (Box 24, Folder 1144)
    - Bowerbank, James Scott, 1797-1877, 1857 (Box 24, Folder 1145)
    - Brande, William Thomas, 1788-1866, 1826 (Box 24, Folder 1146)
    - Brassey, Anne Allnutt, Baroness, 1839- 1887, 1882 (Box 24, Folder 1147)
    - Brayley, E.W. (Edward William), 1802- 1870, 1868 (Box 24, Folder 1148)
    - Breen, James, 1826-1866, undated (Box 24, Folder 1149)
    - Brewster, David, Sir, 1781-1868, 1820-63, undated (Box 24, Folder 1150)
    - Brightwen, Eliza, 1830-1906, 1904 (Box 24, Folder 1151)
    - Bristol, Frederick William Hervey, Marquis of, 1800-1864, 1851 (Box 24, Folder 1152)
    - Bristow, H.W. (Henry William), 1817- 1889, 1870 (Box 24, Folder 1153)
    - Britten, James, 1846-1924, 1904-24 (Box 24, Folder 1154)
    - Brownrigg, William, 1711-1800, undated (Box 24, Folder 1155)
    - Brunel, Henry Marc, 1842-1903, 1900-03, undated (Box 24, Folder 1156)
    - Brunel, Isambard Kingdom, 1806-1859, 1840 (Box 24, Folder 1157)
    - Buch, Leopold von, Freiherr, 1774-1853, 1808 (Box 24, Folder 1158)
    - Buckland, Francis T. (Francis Trevelyan), 1826-1889, undated (Box 24, Folder 1159)
    - Buckland, William, 1784-1856, undated (Box 24, Folder 1160)
    - Burrows, Herbert, 1894 (Box 24, Folder 1161)
    - Busk, George, 1807-1886, 1872 (Box 24, Folder 1162)
    - Callender, Hugh L., 1863-1930, 1904 (Box 24, Folder 1163)
    - Carus, Julius Victor, 1823-1903, 1847 (Box 24, Folder 1164)
    - Carpenter, William Benjamin, 1813-1885, 1867-73 (Box 24, Folder 1165)
    - Carruthers, William, 1830-1922, 1888-98 (Box 24, Folder 1166)
    - Cathcart, Charles Murray Cathcart, Earl, 1783-1859, 1826 (Box 24, Folder 1167)
    - Cayley, George, Sir, 1773-1857, 1839 (Box 24, Folder 1168)
    - Chevallier, Temple, 1794-1873, 1841 (Box 24, Folder 1169)
    - Chough, 1874 (Box 24, Folder 1170)
    - Church, A.H. (Arthur Herbert), 1834- 1915, 1890 (Box 24, Folder 1171)
    - Clarke, John Mason, 1857-1925, 1896 (Box 24, Folder 1172)
    - Clifton, Robert Bellamy, 1836-1921, 1908 (Box 24, Folder 1173)
    - Clodd, Edward, 1840-1930, 1887 (Box 24, Folder 1174)
    - Cockle, James, Sir, 1819-1895, 1892 (Box 24, Folder 1175)
    - Collingwood, Cuthbert, 1826-1908, 1871 (Box 24, Folder 1176)
    - Collins, Benjamin Collins, Sir, 1817- 1880, undated (Box 24, Folder 1177)
    - Collins, Bernard A., 1885 (Box 24, Folder 1178)
    - Congreve, William, Sir, 1772-1828, undated (Box 24, Folder 1179)
    - Conybeare, William Daniel, 1787-1857, undated (Box 24, Folder 1180)
    - Cornish, Vaughan, 1862-1948, 1907 (Box 24, Folder 1181)
    - County of Middlesex Natural History and Science Society, 1886 (Box 24, Folder 1182)
    - Crookes, William, Sir, 1832-1919, 1874 (Box 24, Folder 1183)
    - Cuvier, Georges, 1769-1832, undated (Box 24, Folder 1184)
    - Dalzell, Nicol Alexander, 1817-1878, undated (Box 25, Folder 1185)
    - Dampier, William Cecil Dampier, Sir, 1867-1952, 1904 (Box 25, Folder 1186)
    - Darlington, William, 1782-1863, undated (Box 25, Folder 1187)
    - Darwin, Charles, 1809-1882, 1857, undated (Box 25, Folder 1188)
    - Darwin, Francis, Sir, 1848-1925, 1908 (Box 25, Folder 1189)
    - Darwin, George Howard, Sir, 1845-1912, 1887 (Box 25, Folder 1190)
    - Daubeny, Charles, 1795-1867, 1855 (Box 25, Folder 1191)
    - Davy, Jane, Lady, 1780-1855, undated (Box 25, Folder 1192)
    - Dawkins, William Boyd, 1838-1929, undated (Box 25, Folder 1193)
    - De Morgan, Augustus, 1806-1871, 1850-67 (Box 25, Folder 1194)
    - Derby, Edward Smith Stanley, Earl of, 1775-1851, 1839-46 (Box 25, Folder 1195)
    - DeRoos, Frederick, undated (Box 25, Folder 1196)
    - Dewar, James, Sir, 1842-1923, 1872-83 (Box 25, Folder 1197)
    - Dickinson, Joseph, d. 1865, 1850 (Box 25, Folder 1198)
    - Dickinson, W. Howship (William Howship), 1832-1913, 1862 (Box 25, Folder 1199)
    - Dillwyn, L.W. (Lewis Weston), 1778- 1855, 1837 (Box 25, Folder 1200)
    - Doherty, Henry Latham, 1870-1939, undated (Box 25, Folder 1201)
    - Donkin, W.F. (William Fishburn), 1814- 1869, undated (Box 25, Folder 1202)
    - Druce, G. Claridge (George Claridge), 1850-1932, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 1203)
    - Earle, Maria Theresa Villiers, 1836- 1925, 1910-13 (Box 25, Folder 1204)
    - Edwardes, Tickner, 1865-1944, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 1205)
    - Ellis, Robert Leslie, 1817-1859, undated (Box 25, Folder 1206)
    - Emerson, William, 1701-1782, 1819 (Box 25, Folder 1207)
    - Emery, J.M., 1828 (Box 25, Folder 1208)
    - Evans, John, Sir, 1823-1908, 1876-1905 (Box 25, Folder 1209)
    - Evans, Robert Wilson, 1789-1866, 1847 (Box 25, Folder 1210)
    - Finch, John, 1869 (Box 25, Folder 1211)
    - Fitton, William Henry, 1780-1861, 1810 (Box 25, Folder 1212)
    - Fitzroy, Robert, 1805-1865, 1863 (Box 25, Folder 1213)
    - Flower, Thomas, 1843 (Box 25, Folder 1214)
    - Flower, William Henry, 1831-1899, 1892 (Box 25, Folder 1215)
    - Foster, M. (Michael), Sir, 1836-1907, 1902 (Box 25, Folder 1216)
    - Fourier, Jean Baptiste Joseph, Baron, 1768-1830, undated (Box 25, Folder 1217)
    - Frend, William, 1757-1841, 1825 (Box 25, Folder 1218)
    - Froude, Robert, 1846-1924, 1883 (Box 25, Folder 1219)
    - Galloway, Thomas, 1796-1851, 1844 (Box 25, Folder 1220)
    - Galton, Douglas, Sir, 1822-1899, 1887-91 (Box 25, Folder 1221)
    - Galway, M.B., 1844 (Box 25, Folder 1222)
    - Geikie, Archibald, Sir, 1835-1924, undated (Box 25, Folder 1223)
    - Giberne, Agnes, 1845-1939, 1901-11 (Box 25, Folder 1224)
    - Gibson, Samuel, 1838 (Box 25, Folder 1225)
    - Gilbert, Davies, 1767-1839, 1824-26 (Box 25, Folder 1226)
    - Glaisher, James, 1809-1903, 1865 (Box 25, Folder 1227)
    - Godman, Frederick Du Cane, 1834-1919, 1882-88 (Box 25, Folder 1228)
    - Gordon, Seton, b. 1886, 1923 (Box 25, Folder 1229)
    - Gotch, Francis, 1853-1913, 1895 (Box 25, Folder 1230)
    - Gould, John, 1804-1881 (Box 25, Folder 1231)
    - Gray, John Edward, 1800-1875, 1865-72, undated (Box 25, Folder 1232)
    - Greening, Edward Owen, 1836-1923, 1899 (Box 25, Folder 1233)
    - Grey-Egerton, Philip de Malpas, Sir, Bart, 1806-1881, 1875, undated (Box 25, Folder 1234)
    - Grey of Falloden, Edward Grey, Viscount, 1862-1933, 1896-1928, undated (Box 25, Folder 1235)
    - Greenough, W., 1868 (Box 25, Folder 1236)
    - Gregory, Olinthus, 1774-1841, undated (Box 25, Folder 1237)
    - Greville, Robert Kaye, 1794-1866, undated (Box 25, Folder 1238)
    - Grove, W.R. (William Robert), 1811- 1896, 1866 (Box 25, Folder 1239)
    - Gunther, Albert C.L.G. (Albert Carl Ludwig Gotthilf), 1830-1914, 1887 (Box 25, Folder 1240)
    - Gunther, R.T. (Robert Theodore), 1869- 1940, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 1241)
    - Hadfield, Robert Abbott, Sir, bart., 1858-1940, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 1242)
    - Hall, James, 1811-1898, 1893 (Box 26, Folder 1243)
    - Hampden, Mr., undated (Box 26, Folder 1244)
    - Hampson, George Francis, Sir, 1860- 1936, 1890-91 (Box 26, Folder 1245)
    - Hanbury, Frederick Janson, 1851-1938, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 1246)
    - Hanbury, Thomas, Sir, 1832-1907, 1890 (Box 26, Folder 1247)
    - Hancock, John, 1856 (Box 26, Folder 1248)
    - Harcourt, William Vernon, 1789-1871, undated (Box 26, Folder 1249)
    - Harris, W. Snow (William Snow), 1791- 1867, 1860 (Box 26, Folder 1250)
    - Harrison, Benjamin, 1837-1931, undated (Box 26, Folder 1251)
    - Horsfield, Thomas, 1773-1859, 1819 (Box 26, Folder 1252)
    - Harvey, William H. (William Henry), 1811-1866, 1852 (Box 26, Folder 1253)
    - Hatchett, Charles, 1765?-1847, 1831 (Box 26, Folder 1254)
    - Hawell, John, 1903 (Box 26, Folder 1255)
    - Hawkins, B. Waterhouse (Benjamin Waterhouse), 1807-1889, 1860 (Box 26, Folder 1256)
    - Heard, Gerald, 1889-1971, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 1257)
    - Henslow, John Stevens, 1796-1861, 1829 (Box 26, Folder 1258)
    - Herschel, Alexander Stuart, 1836-1907, 1869 (Box 26, Folder 1259)
    - Herschel, John F.W. (John Frederick William), 1792-1871, undated (Box 26, Folder 1260)
    - Herschel, John, 1837-1921, 1874, undated (Box 26, Folder 1261)
    - Hinde, George Jennings, 1839-1918, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 1262)
    - Hirst, Thomas Archer, 1830-1892, 1875-83 (Box 26, Folder 1263)
    - Hodgkinson, George Christopher, 1816- 1880, 1854 (Box 26, Folder 1264)
    - Hodgson, John, 1779-1845, 1834 (Box 26, Folder 1265)
    - Hoffman, A.W., 1869 (Box 26, Folder 1266)
    - Hogg, Robert, 1818-1897, 1884 (Box 26, Folder 1267)
    - Hole, S. Reynolds (Samuel Reynolds), 1819-1904, undated (Box 26, Folder 1268)
    - Hooker, Joseph Dalton, Sir, 1817-1911, 1867-79, undated (Box 26, Folder 1269)
    - Hooker, William Jackson, Sir, 1785- 1865, 1857-62, undated (Box 26, Folder 1270)
    - Horner, Leonard, 1785-1864, undated (Box 26, Folder 1271)
    - Howard, John Eliot, 1807-1883, undated (Box 26, Folder 1272)
    - Hulme, F. Edward (Frederick Edward), 1841-1909, undated (Box 26, Folder 1273)
    - Hunt, Robert, 1807-1887, 1874 (Box 26, Folder 1274)
    - Hunter, W.B., 1893 (Box 26, Folder 1275)
    - Hutchinson, H.N. (Henry Neville), 1856-1927, 1894 (Box 26, Folder 1276)
    - Huxley, Thomas Henry, 1825-1895, 1867-91, undated (Box 26, Folder 1277)
    - Im Thurn, Everand Ferdinand, Sir, 1852-1932, 1907 (Box 26, Folder 1278)
    - Jeffreys, John Gwyn, 1809-1885, 1871 (Box 26, Folder 1279)
    - Jekyll, Gertrude, 1843-1932, 1910-30 (Box 26, Folder 1280)
    - Jesse, Edward, 1780-1868, 1863-65 (Box 26, Folder 1281)
    - Johnston, George, 1797-1855, undated (Box 26, Folder 1282)
    - Jones, Bence, 1814-1873, undated (Box 26, Folder 1283)
    - Jones, T. Rupert (Thomas Rupert), 1819-1911, 1896 (Box 26, Folder 1284)
    - Jones, Thomas Rymer, 1810-1880, 1840-62 (Box 26, Folder 1285)
    - Judd, John W. (John Wesley), 1840-1916, 1888 (Box 26, Folder 1286)
    - Jukes-Brown, A.J. (Alfred John), 1851- 1914, 1900 (Box 26, Folder 1287)
    - Kearton, Richard, 1862-1928, 1905 (Box 26, Folder 1288)
    - Keith, Arthur, Sir, 1866-1955, 1912 (Box 26, Folder 1289)
    - Kelly, Howard A. (Howard Atwood), 1858-1943, 1904 (Box 26, Folder 1290)
    - Keltie, John Scott, 1840-1927, 1910 (Box 26, Folder 1291)
    - Kelvin, William Thomson, Baron, 1824- 1907, 1905 (Box 26, Folder 1292)
    - Kenealy, Arabella, 1898-1909, undated (Box 26, Folder 1293)
    - Kerr, William, d. 1817, undated (Box 26, Folder 1294)
    - Kiernan, F., 1822 (Box 26, Folder 1295)
    - Kirby, W.F. (William Forsell), 1844- 1912, 1884-89, undated (Box 26, Folder 1296)
    - Lacaita, C.C. (Charles C.), 1853-1933, 1889 (Box 26, Folder 1297)